[
  { "no": 1, "question": "How school years are divided", "answers": "Semesters" },
  { "no": 2, "question": "Cherry (?) viewing ", "answers": "Blossom" },
  { "no": 3, "question": "Time for a trip (?) Week", "answers": "Golden" },
  { "no": 4, "question": "What are the May Blues? ", "answers": "Malaise" },
  { "no": 5, "question": "Where art is shown off and sold", "answers": "Gallery" },
  { "no": 6, "question": "A type of outdoor allergy", "answers": "Pollenosis" },
  { "no": 7, "question": "Nihonga: (?) Cultural artwork", "answers": "Japanese" },
  { "no": 8, "question": "Label for an unparalleled artist", "answers": "Master" },
  { "no": 9, "question": "Held to inform the public ", "answers": "Conference" },
  { "no": 10, "question": "Changes with the season ", "answers": "Wardrobe" },
  { "no": 11, "question": "Exchanged all over the world ", "answers": "Currency" },
  { "no": 12, "question": "A border between air masses", "answers": "Front" },
  { "no": 13, "question": "Medicine of varying legality ", "answers": "Narcotics" },
  { "no": 14, "question": "Many student’s greatest love", "answers": "Vacation" },
  { "no": 15, "question": "These gauge student knowledge ", "answers": "Finals" },
  { "no": 16, "question": "A seasonal skybound event ", "answers": "Fireworks" },
  { "no": 17, "question": "A stationary hotspot: heat (?)", "answers": "Island" },
  { "no": 18, "question": "Necessary for dares", "answers": "Courage" },
  { "no": 19, "question": "A common skin injury", "answers": "Sunburn" },
  { "no": 20, "question": "When it’s too hot to sleep", "answers": "Sweltering" },
  { "no": 21, "question": " Techy term for e-infiltration ", "answers": "Hacking" },
  { "no": 22, "question": "Localized destructive storm ", "answers": "Typhoon" },
  { "no": 23, "question": " Tsukimi: lunar viewing (?)", "answers": "Festival" },
  { "no": 24, "question": "Establishing order and worth ", "answers": "Ranking" },
  { "no": 25, "question": "Absorbs most light", "answers": "Black" }
]
